koromedia.com 2014-04-08

# Privacy Policy.

Koromedia.com (the "Website") is an Internet property of Koromedia company ("us" or "we"). We provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") so that we may inform you about how our technology ("Technology") processes information on behalf of the online advertisers, website owners and other businesses that use our services. This Privacy Policy also outlines our privacy practices on our corporate website ("Website") located at Koromedia Personally Identifiable Information.

We collect Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") from this Website when you attempt to become a Client or otherwise choose to provide PII to us. PII is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to: name, address, telephone number, mobile number and/or email address. For example, you may choose to send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form on our Website. Once collected, we will store your PII for a reasonable period of time for record keeping purposes. The information that we store is sometimes deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business.

## Information Sharing

Koromedia will not sell, share or rent your PII to or with others. Your PII is not shared with any third parties, except: (a) where necessary to conduct business, such as invoicing Clients in connection with the Services or making payments to, or collecting money from, a Client; (b) in the case of a breach of any agreement between Client and Koromedia; (c) where required by law, or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction; (d) (c) in the event of Koromedia bankruptcy, or if Koromedia is sold or acquired; or (e) where Koromedia determines, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of Koromedia and/or a third party, or necessary to protect Koromedia from liability of any kind.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("Non-PII") from Website visitors. Non-PII is information that cannot by itself be used to identify a particular person or entity, and may include your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to our Website, the referring URL and/or your computer's operating system.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We use "cookies" and web beacons to help us manage our Website. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. Web beacons (also known as "1x1 pixels" or "clear GIFs") are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. Web users have the option of blocking the use of cookies by changing a setting in their browser. Web users can check their browser supplier's website for details on how to do this. For more information about cookies and web beacons please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies>.

## Third Party Websites

This Website may contain links to and advertisements for websites operated by third parties whose privacy practices may differ from those of Koromedia. While we endeavor to associate only with reputable entities, Koromedia cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites. We encourage you to check the privacy policies of all websites that you visit.

## Minors

This Website is not intended for visitors that are under eighteen (18) years of age. Koromedia does not knowingly solicit or collect information from individuals under the age of eighteen (18). If we determine that we have inadvertently collected PII from someone under eighteen (18) years of age, we will take reasonable steps to purge this information from our database. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the Internet activities of their children.

## Security

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we also do everything in our power to protect PII (including Sensitive Information) off-line. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect our end-users' PII, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Once we receive the transmission of your PII, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All our end-users' PII is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example a customer service representative) are granted access to PII. Employees not adhering to our policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state law, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your PII. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy & Notification of Changes

Koromedia reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a clear and conspicuous notice on the Website explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Please check the Website periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Website and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

## Deleting your PII

If you'd like us to delete any PII that you have provided to us on our Website, please send your request to us and we will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt.

## Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of Koromedia, please feel free to [contact us](http://koromedia.com/contacts).
